blogmad.net 2007-07-21

# Blog Mad - the Blog Traffic Exchange // BETA

## Overview

_Privacy Policy Statement of KinetiQ.org and all related websites._

_The following websites are covered by this Privacy Statement;

KinetiQ.org  
Vault9.net  
BlogMad.net   
BlogHack  
Blixels  
BlogSrc

_  
This privacy policy document serves to represent the KinetiQ.org stance on privacy. 

**General**   
We at The KinetiQ Web Movement are extremely committed to ensuring that everyone who accesses any of our sites can be happy in the knowledge that their information is not only private, but also secure. 

Back to top

**Security**   
All passwords used across the KinetiQ network are run through a one way hash before being stored meaning that even if someone were able to get hold of our database they wouldn't be able to crack the passwords. 

The Bloghack program is purely fun and no damage, permanent or otherwise is done to any website or web server that can be defined as hacking. 

Hacking is defined as unauthorized access to computer systems. 

Back to top

**Personal Information**   
All your personal information is secure and safe and will NEVER be sold or given to 3rd parties unless by legal request with a valid subpoena.   
Your sex, age and all other demographical information are recorded for statistical purposes only and will never be sold or disclosed to 3rd parties.   
This statistical data may be used to create targetted advertising campaigns but will never disclose any of your personal information. 

Back to top

**Email Addresses and Contact Details**   
Your email address will only ever be used by the administration team to distribute any newsletters distributed by KinetiQ.org or any related sites. All newsletters are an Opt in / Opt out personal user preference. All other correspondence will be done via the sites interfaces unless circumstances prevent usage of the messaging or support ticketing systems. KinteiQ will not sell trade or give your email address and other contact information to other 3rd parties. In the spirit of a greater user experience, KinetiQ Administration will inform you of other blogging and / or ventures which are controlled by KinetiQ and NOT by 3rd parties. We strive to add value to the social online culture and will inform all our members of new happenings, sites, benefits and features applicable to our partner sites as well as blogging, the blogger community and blog culture. 

Back to top

**Cookies**   
The KinetiQ websites makes use of cookies which are not aggressive information harvesting cookies but are used to store session information such as the age of the session as well as to store your personal site preferences. 

Back to top

**External Sites**   
The KinetiQ websites are structured in a way that there are a number of links pointing to other websites from within the sites. 

Bloghack, Vault9, BlogSrc, BlogMad and Blixels are official KinetiQ partner websites and are run and maintained by The KinetiQ Web Movement. These websites can at times interact between databases.All information passed between the websites is covered by this privacy policy. 

The KinetiQ Web Movement are not responsible in anyway for the content of any websites or blogs that use any our services.

While we do deploy methods of preventing anyone from contravening our terms, we cannot make any gurantees that all filters and content management will always be successful, although we do deploy a group of volunteer moderators across all sites so as to lend the human touch in assisting to keep our terms adhered to. 

Back to top

**User Spam**   
Spam is not welcome and will NOT be tolerated.   
Any user using any feature of any KinetiQ website to spam, regardless of the nature of the spam, will be in contravention of our terms of usage and will be warned. 

Repeat offenders will be banned. 

Banning on a first offence is subject to the severity of the contravention of the spam rule. 

“Spam” is defined as communicating any unsolicited, blatantly advertorial and/or inappropriate message via email or online community sites such as message boards, forums (and their shout boxes), or anyone else’s web log. 

Any queries can be addressed to   
support@kinetiq.org 

Any contraventions can be reported by sending email to  
abuse@kinetiq.org

Back to top

**The simple version.**

While the above may sound like a lot of legal mumbo jumbo,   
all that it says is that we promise never to sell your information to anyone,   
your email addresses and personal information are safe and your password is encrypted to be hacker proof.
